const quizData = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is the name of Ross' second wife?",
      options: ["Emily", "Carol", "Janice", "Susan"],
      answer: "Emily"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "What is the name of Joey's stuffed penguin?",
      options: ["Hugsy", "Waddles", "Snowy", "Penny"],
      answer: "Hugsy"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Which character famously says 'How you doin'?'",
      options: ["Joey", "Ross", "Chandler", "Monica"],
      answer: "Joey"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Where does Ross work?",
      options: ["Central Perk", "Museum of Natural History", "Chandler's office", "BLOOMINGDALE'S"],
      answer: "Museum of Natural History"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "What is the name of the coffee shop the friends frequently visit?",
      options: ["Central Cafe", "Coffee Place", "Central Perk", "Perk Central"],
      answer: "Central Perk"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Which friend is a chef?",
      options: ["Monica", "Rachel", "Phoebe", "Joey"],
      answer: "Monica"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What is the name of Ross and Monica's dog?",
      options: ["Spot", "Fido", "Marcel", "Chi-Chi"],
      answer: "Chi-Chi"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Which character sings 'Smelly Cat'?",
      options: ["Rachel", "Phoebe", "Monica", "Joey"],
      answer: "Phoebe"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Who gets stuck in a pair of leather pants?",
      options: ["Ross", "Chandler", "Joey", "Monica"],
      answer: "Ross"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "What is Joey's catchphrase?",
      options: ["How you doin'?", "Smelly Cat", "We were on a break!", "Could I BE any more..."],
      answer: "How you doin'?"
    }
  ];

  export default quizData;